Ground collision. Jet engine. Ground support vehicle. Wet airfield pavement. Engine nacelle damage. White tug or pushback vehicle. Now listen and repeat. This picture depicts a ground collision. I can see a commercial aircraft on the ground. Its jet engine appears to have collided with a ground support vehicle. The pavement looks wet. There is visible damage to the engine nacelle. This looks like a serious ground incident.
Now listen to a stronger version.
This picture depicts the aftermath of a severe ground collision between a commercial aircraft and a ground support vehicle.
The engine nacelle is visibly damaged.
This suggests that a significant impact occurred during ground operations.
Now listen to the full exam version.
This picture depicts the aftermath of a severe ground collision between a commercial airliner's jet engine and a ground support vehicle on a wet airfield pavement.
Visible damage to the engine nacelle suggests a significant impact occurred during ground operations, clearly involving a white tug or pushback vehicle.
Now say it yourself using these words.
Ground collision.
Commercial aircraft.
Jet engine.
Ground support vehicle.
Wet pavement.
Engine nacelle damage.
Ground operations.
White tug or pushback vehicle.
Now repeat the final version one more time.
This picture depicts the aftermath of a severe ground collision between a commercial aircraft and a ground support vehicle.
Visible damage to the engine nacelle suggests that a significant impact occurred during ground operations.
This picture depicts the aftermath of a serious ground collision involving a commercial aircraft and a ground support vehicle.
The aircraft’s engine nacelle appears to be damaged, which suggests a significant impact during ground operations.
The pavement looks wet, and the vehicle involved seems to be a white tug or pushback vehicle.
This picture depicts a serious ground incident.
A commercial aircraft appears to have collided with a ground support vehicle.
The engine looks damaged, and the pavement appears to be wet.