Off-field emergency landing. Light propeller aircraft. Elevated roadway. Visible airframe damage. Blocking traffic. Emergency personnel. Securing the area. Now listen and repeat. This picture depicts an off-field emergency landing. I can see a light propeller aircraft on an elevated roadway. The aircraft appears to be damaged. It is blocking traffic. Emergency personnel are securing the area. This looks like a serious emergency situation.
Now listen to a stronger version. This picture depicts the aftermath of an apparent off-field emergency landing. It involves a light propeller aircraft on an elevated roadway. The airframe has sustained visible damage. The aircraft is blocking traffic, while emergency personnel are securing the area. Now listen to the full exam version.
This picture depicts the aftermath of an apparent off-field emergency landing involving a light propeller aircraft on an elevated roadway.
The airframe has sustained visible damage and is blocking traffic, while emergency personnel are securing the area.
Now say it yourself using these words.
Off-field emergency landing.
Light propeller aircraft.
Elevated roadway.
Visible damage.
Blocking traffic.
Emergency personnel.
Securing the area.
Now repeat the final version one more time.
This picture depicts the aftermath of an apparent off-field emergency landing involving a light propeller aircraft on an elevated roadway.
The airframe has sustained visible damage and is blocking traffic, while emergency personnel are securing the area.
This picture depicts the aftermath of an off-field emergency landing involving a light propeller aircraft.
The aircraft appears to have landed on an elevated roadway and has sustained visible damage.
It is blocking traffic, while emergency personnel are securing the area.
This picture depicts an emergency landing.
I can see a light propeller aircraft on a roadway.
The aircraft is damaged and emergency personnel are securing the area.