Wide-body military transport aircraft. High-speed roll after touchdown. Runway deceleration. Engine thrust reversers. Wing spoilers. Fully deployed. Now listen and repeat. This picture depicts a military transport aircraft after landing. I can see a wide-body aircraft on the runway. The aircraft appears to be in the high-speed rolling phase after touchdown. It looks like the aircraft is decelerating on the runway.
The thrust reversers and wing spoilers are deployed. This looks like a normal landing roll. Now listen to a stronger version.
This picture depicts a wide-body military transport aircraft during the high-speed rolling phase of flight after touchdown.
The situation looks like a standard deceleration on the runway.
Both engine thrust reversers and wing spoilers appear to be fully deployed.
Now listen to the full exam version.
This picture depicts a wide-body military transport aircraft during the high-speed rolling phase of flight after touchdown.
The situation looks like a standard high-energy deceleration on the runway, with both engine thrust reversers and wing spoilers fully deployed.
Now say it yourself using these words.
Wide-body military transport aircraft.
High-speed rolling phase.
After touchdown.
Runway.
High-energy deceleration.
Engine thrust reversers.
Wing spoilers.
Fully deployed.
Now repeat the final version one more time.
This picture depicts a wide-body military transport aircraft during the high-speed rolling phase of flight after touchdown.
The situation looks like a standard high-energy deceleration on the runway, with both engine thrust reversers and wing spoilers fully deployed.
This picture depicts a wide-body military transport aircraft after landing.
The aircraft appears to be in the high-speed rolling phase on the runway after touchdown.
It looks like a normal deceleration, with thrust reversers and wing spoilers fully deployed.
This picture depicts a military transport aircraft after landing.
It is rolling on the runway at high speed.
The aircraft appears to be slowing down, with thrust reversers and spoilers deployed.
```