Standard airport operation. Commercial aircraft. Parked on the apron. Passenger boarding. Maintenance. Normal operation. Mountain ridge. Airfield background. Now listen and repeat. This picture depicts a normal airport operation. I can see a commercial aircraft parked on the apron. The aircraft may be prepared for passenger boarding. It may also be undergoing maintenance. The operation seems completely normal.
A prominent mountain ridge is visible behind the airfield. Now listen to a stronger version. This appears to be a standard operational scenario. A commercial aircraft is parked on the apron. It may be there for passenger boarding or maintenance. The situation looks normal and well controlled. A mountain ridge is visible directly behind the airfield. Now listen to the full exam version.
This appears to be a standard operational scenario where a commercial aircraft is parked on the apron for passenger boarding or maintenance.
The operation seems completely normal, and a prominent mountain ridge is visible directly behind the airfield.
Now say it yourself using these words.
Standard operational scenario.
Commercial aircraft.
Parked on the apron.
Passenger boarding.
Maintenance.
Normal operation.
Mountain ridge.
Behind the airfield.
Now repeat the final version one more time.
This appears to be a standard operational scenario where a commercial aircraft is parked on the apron for passenger boarding or maintenance.
The operation seems completely normal, and a prominent mountain ridge is visible directly behind the airfield.
This picture depicts a normal airport operation involving a commercial aircraft.
The aircraft appears to be parked on the apron, possibly for passenger boarding or maintenance.
The situation looks normal and well controlled, with a prominent mountain ridge visible behind the airfield.
This picture depicts a normal airport operation.
I can see a commercial aircraft parked on the apron.
The aircraft may be prepared for boarding or maintenance.