Severe incident. Forced water landing. Runway excursion. Lake. Light single-engine aircraft. Partially submerged. Nose-first. Nose-over position. Now listen and repeat. This picture depicts a severe incident. I can see a light single-engine aircraft in the water. The aircraft is partially submerged nose-first. It appears to be in a nose-over position. This may have been a forced water landing.
It could also have been a runway excursion into a lake. Now listen to a stronger version. This picture depicts the aftermath of a severe incident. It may have been a forced water landing or a runway excursion into a lake. A light single-engine aircraft is partially submerged nose-first. The airframe shows a clear sign of a nose-over position. Now listen to the full exam version.
This picture depicts the aftermath of a severe incident, possibly a forced water landing or a runway excursion into a lake.
A light single-engine aircraft is partially submerged nose-first, with its airframe showing a clear sign of a nose-over position.
Now say it yourself using these words.
Severe incident.
Forced water landing.
Runway excursion.
Lake.
Light single-engine aircraft.
Partially submerged.
Nose-first.
Nose-over position.
Now repeat the final version one more time.
This picture depicts the aftermath of a severe incident, possibly a forced water landing or a runway excursion into a lake.
A light single-engine aircraft is partially submerged nose-first, with its airframe showing a clear sign of a nose-over position.
This picture depicts the aftermath of a serious incident involving a light single-engine aircraft.
The aircraft appears to be partially submerged nose-first in the water.
This may have been a forced water landing or a runway excursion into a lake.
This picture depicts a serious incident.
I can see a light aircraft in the water.
The aircraft is partially submerged and appears to be nose-first.
```