Landing incident. Regional turboprop airliner. Low-visibility conditions. Nose gear failure. Forward fuselage. Runway surface. Direct contact with the runway. Now listen and repeat. This picture depicts a landing incident. I can see a regional turboprop airliner on the runway. The visibility appears to be low. The aircraft seems to have suffered a nose gear failure. The forward fuselage is in direct contact with the runway surface.
This looks like a serious landing incident. Now listen to a stronger version. This picture depicts a landing incident involving a regional turboprop airliner. The aircraft appears to be operating under low-visibility conditions. It seems to have suffered a nose gear failure. As a result, the forward fuselage is making direct contact with the runway surface. Now listen to the full exam version.
This picture depicts a landing incident involving a regional turboprop airliner under low-visibility conditions.
The aircraft seems to have suffered a nose gear failure, causing the forward fuselage to make direct contact with the runway surface.
Now say it yourself using these words.
Landing incident.
Regional turboprop airliner.
Low visibility.
Nose gear failure.
Forward fuselage.
Runway surface.
Direct contact.
Now repeat the final version one more time.
This picture depicts a landing incident involving a regional turboprop airliner under low-visibility conditions.
The aircraft seems to have suffered a nose gear failure, causing the forward fuselage to make direct contact with the runway surface.
This picture depicts a landing incident involving a regional turboprop airliner.
The visibility appears to be low, and the aircraft seems to have suffered a nose gear failure.
As a result, the forward fuselage is in direct contact with the runway surface.
This picture depicts a landing incident.
I can see a regional turboprop aircraft on the runway.
The nose gear appears to have failed, and the front part of the aircraft is touching the runway.